# YAKUP **BUDANCAMANAK**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# Skills

## Skill group

C# Python lava **VB.NET** HTML,CSS,JS Flask ASP.NET MVC Android React.js SQL

### Languages

English

# Interests

#### **Sports**

Love watching and playing football, basketball.

# Contact

- ★ Istanbul
- **1** +90 507 777 26 82
- budancamanak@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/yakupbudancamanak-05254159
- @budancamanak3

# **About**

Talented full-stack software development professional with 10 years of experience in software development. Consistent in delivering clean, error-free, reliable code to meet current or expected needs. Well-versed in software trends and confident in multiple languages, frameworks and programming tools.

# Experience

#### **2017 - Present** ViraSoft Yazılım Ticaret A. Ş

Software Engineer Team Lead, Istanbul Design, implement, test and documents projects for digital pathology sector. Developed web application to be used as a host application for in-house developed Al analysis algorithms.

Developed education platform to be used by pathology institutions

Developed image management system to be used within hospitals and lab environments

Used multiple languages and frameworks throughout the processes. Have experience with HIPAA Have experience with FDA regulations and documentations.

#### 2014 - 2016 Maksan Proje Taahhüt Ltd Şti

Software Engineer, Istanbul Designed and implemented custom ERP solution

Developed android application to integrate with ERP solution.

Implemented features to integrate ERP solution to AutoCad application.



## Başar Bilişim

Software Developer, Istanbul Design and implement software projects for web and android platforms.

Implemented features and bug fixes to online shopping web sites Created custom ERP solution for healthy food delivery company. Created android application to be used with custom bluetooth medical device.

2012 - 2013

### Cardtek

Junior Software Developer, Istanbul Designed and developed .NET forms applications for back-office usages. Implemented web services to be used for external integrations with customers.

# Education

2008 - Present

## **Computer Engineering**

Yıldız Technical University, Istanbul

2004 - 2008

## **High School**

Abdülkerim Bengi Anadolu High School, Mer sin